Tin Soldier is a action, thriller film directed by Brad Furman.
An ex-special forces operative seeks revenge against a cult leader
who has corrupted his former comrades, the Shinjas.
This leader, known as The Bokushi, promises veterans a purpose and
protection, but is revealed to be a destructive influence.
The ex-soldier, Nash Cavanaugh, joins forces with military operative Emmanuel Ashburn
to infiltrate the Bokushi's fortress and expose his reign of terror
Nash Cavanaugh, played by Scott Eastwood.
The Bokushi, played by Jamie Foxx.
Emmanuel Ashburn, played by Robert De Niro.
Evoli, played by Nora Arnezeder.
Lido Rossi, played by Joey Bicicchi.
Luke, played by John Leguizamo.
Tin Soldier is a 2025 American action thriller film directed by Brad
Furman, written by Furman, Jess Fuerst, and Pablo Fenjves.
It stars Scott Eastwood, John Leguizamo, Nora
Arnezeder, Jamie Foxx, and Robert De Niro.
Filmed in 2022, it was not released until 2025, and
was overwhelmingly disliked by critics.
The film explores themes of mysterious, angry, conceited.
The tone is intense.